阿历克斯...
Alex...
你做我最好的朋友有20年了
You've been my best friend for 20 years.
没了你 我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what I would do without you.
毫不夸张地说 我会活不下去
I literally would not want to live.
但现在这都不再是问题
But I don't have to think about that ever again
因为我将和你共度余生...
because I get to spend the rest of my life with...
停!
Stop!
我反对!
I object!
那是谁?
Who is that?
阿历克斯 我爱你!
Alex, I love you!
- 怎么回事? - 我没参加彩排
- What... what's happening here? - I skipped the rehearsal,
但我很确定那男人爱阿历克斯
but I'm pretty sure that guy's in love with Alex.
别答应! 你亲口告诉我
Don't do this! You told me yourself
你压根不知道自己是否还爱他
that you don't even know if you still love him,
还有他总是忘乎所以还有...
and that he let himself go and that...
性爱很糟糕
That the sex was bad.
嘿 兄弟! 我祖母在
Shh! Hey, man! My Nana's here.
阿历克斯 我爱你
Alex, I love you.
跟我走吧
Come with me.
我觉得我们该
Yo, I feel like we're supposed to
- 狠揍他一顿 - 你上 你是老黑
- kick this guy's ass or something. - You do it. You're black.
他可能已经吓到了
He's probably already scared of you.
没错 但你是同性恋又胖嘟嘟的
Yeah, but you're gay and chubby.
- 他会防不胜防的 - 胖嘟嘟?
- No one will see it coming. - Chubby?
戴夫 抱歉
Dave, I'm sorry.
我办不到
I can't do this.
我来了
I'm coming. Okay.
给力!
Kick-ass!
哇哦!
Whoo!
- 她肯定会回来的 - 她绝对会后悔
- I'm sure she'll be right back. - She's totally regretting this decision.
会没事的 我保证
It's gonna be okay. I promise you.
剧情大反转
Huge game changer. Huge.
额 我...
Uh, I'm... uh...
我很遗憾 兄弟 糟透了
I'm sorry, bro. Sucks.
幸福终点站
第一季  第01集
=深影字幕组=
- 哇哦 - 溜冰鞋?
- Wow. - Rollerblades?
连我都觉得穿溜冰鞋的是同性恋
Even I think rollerblades are gay,
我昨天和一男人上床了
and I had sex with a dude last night.
我知道她是你姐妹 宝贝
I mean, I know she's your sister and everything, babe,
但那实在是冷血
but that was cold-blooded.
- 你现在真的不喝酒? - 对的
- Are you really not drinking right now? - Nope.
因为我宁愿认为
'Cause I would like to think
如果这事发生在我马萨诸塞州的同性恋婚礼上
that if this happened at my Massachusetts Civil Union,
而你又是伴郎 你会处于一种酒后胡言的状态
and you were the best man, you would be schlammered.
简和我处于备孕期
Jane and I are on our prepregnancy cleanse.
不准吃肉 不准吃糖 不准喝酒
No meat, no sugar, no booze.
我喜欢保持子宫清洁
I like to keep a tidy uterus.
她是这样
She does.
戴夫给我发了短信 他说不想说话
Oh, Dave just texted me. Okay, he says he doesn't wanna talk,
但他..."一切都很好"? 哇哦
but that he's... "All good in the hood"? Whoa.
为什么?
Why?!
敬我们的最后一次相聚
Mm. Well, here's to the last time we were ever all together.
他们能解决的
They could still work this out.
你疯了吗? 你是疯子吗? 你发疯了吗?
Are you crazy? Are you a crazy person? Have you lost your mind?
因为阿历克斯和戴夫再也不可能
Because Alex and Dave will never be able
出现在同一间屋子里
to be in the same room together again.
也可能一个星期后 我们都回到教堂
Or a week from now, we're all gonna be back at the church,
戴夫和阿历克斯也在那
and Dave and Alex are gonna be there,
我们都说笑着
and we're gonna be laughing
"落跑新娘是什么情况?"
like, "What Runaway Bride situation?"
#越是淡然#
And the less I seek my source for some definitive
#生活越是自在#
the closer I am to fine
#耶#
yeah
#生活越是自在#
the closer I am to fine
#耶#
yeah
#我去见哲学博士#
I went to see the doctor of philosophy
阿历克斯?
Alex?
嘿 同伴们
Oh. Hey, guys.
怎么啦?
Wassup?
- 嘿! 你咋样? - 嘿 怎么样?
- Hey! How you doing? - Hey. How's it going?
嘿 甜心!
Hey, sweetie!
很好 相当好 好的不得了
Great. Really great. I'm kicking ass.
我做了很多事 做在线瑜伽
I've been doing lots of stuff.  Uh, taking online yoga,
见识牛人 他们叫我"菩提"
meeting great people. They're calling me "Bodhi,"
太酷了 因为终极豪情(男主角也叫菩提)
which is awesome 'cause of "Point Break."
-看了好多遍 百看不厌 是吧? - 不错
- Been watching that a lot. Totally holds up. Right? - Good.
小洛丽怎么了 对吧?
What happened to Lori petty, right?
喔! 我还发明了新饮品
Oh! I invented a new drink. Ooh!
谁想尝尝杜松子思慕雪
Who wants to try a gin smoothie?
疯了
Crazy.
加点这个 多放点那个
Little bit of this, lot of that. Uh...
顺便提一下...彭妮多谢你的搅拌机
Sidebar... Penny, thanks for the blender.
很棒
It's awesome.
好了 嘿 嘿 甜心
Okay, hey, hey, sweetie,
你和阿历克斯会没事的
you and Alex are gonna work this out.
这只是你们轰轰烈烈的爱情故事中
This is just the sad chapter
一段悲伤的小插曲
in your epic love story.
这是经典桥段 男孩遇见女孩
Ah, this is a classic story of boy meets girl,
因为某滑轮男 男孩失去了女孩
boy loses girl to guy on rollerblades,
男孩成了视频网站上的轰动人物
boy becomes biggest YouTube sensation
就像 "困在大号里的猫猫"
since "Kitten Stuck in Tuba."
被传上视频网了?
It's on YouTube?
点击量如何?-也没多少
How many hits? -Oh, barely any.
戴夫 我要帮你转变下思想 因为我爱你
Dave, I'm gonna break it down for you because I love you.
你的婚礼糟透了 我是说 就像
Your wedding was horrible. I mean, it was like
主日学校的鲨鱼袭击
a shark attack at a Sunday school.
但好的方面来看
But there is a positive,
你现在单身啦
and that is that you are single right now.
所以为何不穿上裤子? 一起去找点乐子
So why don't you go get some pants on?  And let's get you some sex.
我不想找乐子 我想结婚
I don't want to get some sex. I wanna get some married...
和阿历克斯
Oh.  To Alex.
我不明白 是...是她说性爱很糟糕的吗?
I don't get it, you guys.  Did...Did she say the sex was bad?
你知道...每段感情都有喜有悲 亲爱的
You know... Every relationship has its ups and downs, sweetie.
这值得好好讨论一下
Yeah, I mean, it was a big topic of conversation.
我一直觉得是她的错
I just always thought it was her fault.
我意思是 我可能是有点偷懒
I mean, I might've gotten lazy.
用了些同样的动作
You know, recycled some moves.
但那么说太恶劣了
But that is s-so bad.
戴夫 你正散发着霍华德·休斯的气息
Dave, you're giving off a real Howard Hughes vibe here.
我感觉再过十分钟
I feel like you're about ten minutes away
你就该用罐子装尿了
from storing your urine in jars.
一起去吃点东西吧
Let's go get you some food.
我刚吃了三个法式披萨
- I just ate three French bread pizzas
和一大半世界上最大的新娘巧克力
and most of the world's largest chocolate bride.
- 我把手留着...用来握着 - 好吧
- I left the hand... to hold. - Okay.
同伴们 我没事 我很好
Guys, I'm okay. I'm good.
我需要放松 充充电
I'm just gonna kick back. You know, recharge the battery.
再说 我还有一堆感谢信要写
Besides, I-I got a ton of thank you notes to write.
"黑暗的时期
"Darkness reigns.
希望呼出死亡的气息"
Hope gurgles out its dying breath."
"谢谢你漂亮的瓦罐"
"Thank you for the beautiful crock-pot."
好吧 你不能寄这个
Okay, you can't send this.
只是个草稿 同伴们 我会没事的 好不?
It's a rough draft. Guys, I'm gonna be fine, all right?
我只是需要一个人待着 一点私人时间
I-I just need a little me time. You know, a little "D." time.
再说 也许阿历克斯接着就打电话来了
Besides, Alex's next move is probably gonna be to call,
所以我应该...守着电话
so I should... stay close to the phone.
她肯定会打来的
She's definitely gonna call.
她和滑轮男度蜜月去了
She went on the honeymoon with the Rollerblade guy.
拿裤子给我
Somebody get me some pants.
#她让她的战利品跳起来#
She make her booty bounce, bounce, b-bounce...
我有种背叛阿历克斯的感觉
I kind of feel like we're cheating on Alex. I know.
你没必要告诉他她去度蜜月了
You did not have to tell him that she went on the honeymoon.
这让她看起来很坏
It makes her look bad.
不 是她做的坏事让她看起来很坏
No, Alex looks bad because she's doing bad stuff.
对 就像约翰·梅尔的歌
Yeah, that's like saying John Mayer's songs
让他看起来很坏
are making John Mayer look bad.
耶
Yeah.
啊
Ahh.
我喜欢你的纹身
I love your tattoo.
只是用来提醒我要脚踏实地
It really just reminds me to stay grounded.
- 这是我听过最蠢的 - 什么?
- That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard. - What?
我说 "我爱脚踏实地"!
I said, "I love staying grounded"!
领悟到了!
Get it!
- 哇哦! 那是我朋友 - 她很特别
- Whoa! That's my friend, son. - She is... she is a special girl.
- 谁干的? - #让它跳起来#
- Who does that? - Make it bounce, make it bounce
#让它跳起来 耶#
make it bounce, make it bounce, yeah
嗷 嗷
Ow. Ow.
阿历克斯?
Alex?
- 嗨 - 就来说这个?
- Hi. - That's what you're going with?
戴夫 别这样
Dave, come on.
听着...
Listen...
我知道没什么我能说的
I know there's nothing that I can say.
请你明白我真的很抱歉
Please know that I'm so sorry.
顺便问一下 那男的是你男朋友吗?
So is that guy your boyfriend, by the way?
- 谁? 波? - 啊 他当然叫波
- Who? Bo? - Ah, of course his name is Bo.
他可能在修脚趾
He probably shaves his toes.
不 不 不 他不是我男朋友
No, no, no, no, no. He's not my boyfriend.
我们只是工作的时候眉来眼去而已
We flirted a little bit at work.
但我不知道为什么他认为我会跟他私奔（跑了）
But I have no idea why he thought I'd run away with him.
呃...因为你就是跟他跑了
Uh... because you did.
顺便问下 蜜月怎样?
And how was our honeymoon, by the way?
波对日落情侣按摩套餐
Did Bo enjoy the sunset couples massage
-以及跟你嘿咻还满意吗? - 什么啊!?
- and the having sex with you?! - What?
我从没给你戴过绿帽 波也没跟我一起度蜜月
I never cheated on you, and Bo didn't go with me.
听好 戴夫 我没跟他私奔
Listen, Dave, I didn't run away with him.
我只是...逃婚了
I just... ran away.
我被你这些傻逼辫子晃瞎眼了好吗!
I can't believe that you got the white trash tourist braids!
跟个铁血战士一样!我觉得你都要
You look like Predator! I feel like you're gonna
把我抽筋剔骨 拿我的天灵盖当战利品了!
rip my spine out and keep my skull as a trophy!
我道歉 可以吗?
I'm sorry. Okay?
但是我犹豫再三很久了
But I've been having second thoughts for a while.
我是指 好好回想过去几年
I mean, think about the past few years.
坦诚讲 你觉得我们之间还如往昔吗?
Can you honestly say they still felt the same?
当然啊!
- Yes!
情人节快乐 宝贝儿
Happy Valentine's Day, baby.
40块现金?(情人节礼物)
$40?
别客气啦
You're welcome.
阿历克斯 我长这么大 喜欢的只有你
Alex, you're the only girl I've ever even liked.
我甚至都不能想象自己下半辈子
I literally can't even picture myself with another woman
会和别的女人共度余生
ever again for the rest of my life.
你看见我的舌环了吗?
Have you seen my tongue ring?
妈啊 我不是又吞了一枚吧
God, I hope I didn't swallow another one.
我不知道那人是谁
I do not know who that is.
噢 难以置信啊他竟然跟“脚踏实地”女上床了
Ugh! I can't believe he slept with the "stay grounded" girl.
竟然还是在我们的床上
In our bed.
竟然还是我在准新娘派对送给你的床单上?
- On the sheets I got you for the bridal shower?
知不知道姐千辛万苦
Do you know how hard
才给你弄来这个埃及棉床单的啊?
it is to get slut out of Egyptian cotton?
你们怎么能让他带女人回家呢
I can't believe you guys let him go home with another girl.
好吧 你现在好像没资格
Okay, you're not really in a position right now
来说别人怎么可以在不合适的时间
to comment on people leaving places
跟不合适的人离开吧
with people that they're not supposed to leave with.
加油 彭妮!加油 彭妮你个没用的东西
Come on, Penny! Come on, Penny, you piece of garbage.
加油跑啊 彭妮!
Come on, Penny!
彭妮跑啊!彭妮跑起来
Penny, please! Penny, please.
- 给我跑起来 彭妮! - 彭妮悠着点
Do this, Penny! Penny, take it easy.
欢迎重回单身 阿力
Welcome back to the single life, Al.
单身世界竞争很激烈的
It has gotten competitive out there.
走起来 姐妹们 该去锻炼臀大肌了!
Let's go, ladies. It's time to blast our glutes!
之前十年你都没交往过别的男人
While you've been spooning for ten years,
游戏规则早就变了
the whole game changed.
现在的男人甚至都不打电话
A guy doesn't even have to call anymore.
半夜给你发个短信就跟和你吃了烛光晚餐似的
A text at midnight is basically a romantic dinner for two.
- 想要跟你上床 - 我说 为什么不
- Hope you're ready to put out. - You know, why don't you just
把戴夫也叫来今晚彭妮的派对
pull Dave aside tonight at Penny's party
然后你跟他好好谈谈?你们总得相互给个说法
and just talk to him?  You guys are gonna work this out.
他肯定会原谅你的
He's definitely gonna forgive you.
你那天难道没在婚礼现场吗?
Were you not at the wedding?
没有比这更好的了 信我
There's nothing better out there, trust me.
就一堆穷鬼 脑子里全是奇奇怪怪的性幻想
It's just a bunch of poor guys with, like, weird sexual stuff.
甚至是当你都同意跟他们上床
And even when you do it,
他们都不会打个电话来的
they still don't call.
彭 我在想 那个
Pen, I was thinking, you know,
我今晚不去行吗?
is it okay if maybe I don't come tonight?
我不想惹出麻烦
I don't want to cause any drama.
真的?你不来我的30岁生日派对?
Really? You're not gonna come to my 30th birthday party?
那我要给托德打个电话你不来了
I'll just tell Todd that you couldn't make it.
你不想见他
You didn't want to meet him.
不好意思 托德是谁来着?
- I'm sorry. Who's Todd again?
未来黑利 麦迪逊 和麦肯齐他爸
Only the future father to Hailey, Madison, and Mackenzie.
对 - 呃 不好意思 夫人
Right. Um, excuse me, ma'am.
你用完这个机器了吗?
Are you done with this machine?
"夫人"?
"Ma'am"?
姐要出去骂一下街
I am gonna go and bawl my eyes out,
然后回来跟你肉搏
and then I will be back to physically fight you.
兄弟 我好兴奋哦我们要做室友了
Dude, I am so pumped we're gonna be roomies.
是啊 跟大学时候一样 除了你现在肥了一圈
Yeah, it'll be like college again, except now you're chubby.
肥了一圈?这件事 就这么说不腻吗?
Chubby? Is that, like, a thing that is being talked about?
知道不 兄弟 我跟简有了这房子以后
Know what, bro? When Jane and I get this house,
你就应该搬过来住
you should come live with us.
就是啊 这穷乡僻壤的单身的也只有
- Yeah,  the only single people in the suburbs are
恋童癖和拉拉指导顾问了
pedophiles and lesbian guidance counselors.
啊哦 布莱特 看看谁来了
Uh-oh, Brad. Look who's here.
你的老朋友肉肉回来了
Your old friend meat is back.
嗯 不用了  兄弟
Mm. I'm good, bro.
简中午给我做了好吃的
Jane made me a nice lunch.
哦!哦!兄弟
Ugh! Ugh! Man, oh,
那味道跟个欧洲篮球运动员发出来的味道一样
that smells like a European basketball player.
呃
Mmm.
"封山育林"太痛苦了
This cleanse is brutal.
我瘦了11磅...今天
I lost 11 pounds... today..
重要事 今晚去彭妮的派对吗?
More importantly, are you coming to Penny's party, bro?
他要带个新人过来 肯定又很好笑
She's bringing a new dude, which is always hi-larious.
拜托 我当然要去了
Dude, of course I'm coming to Penny's party.
干嘛不去?因为阿历克斯吗?
Why wouldn't I be? Because of Alex?
我是个成年人 我会用成年人的方式处理问题
I am an adult, and I'm gonna handle this like an adult.
大家好啊!
Wassup?!
嗯
Mm.
历史性的夜晚
Best night ever.
马克斯 简 你们还记得杰姬吧
Max, Jane, you remember Jackie.
嗨
Hi.
哦!嘿 没想到你会来啊
Oh! Hey. Didn't realize you were gonna be at this thing.
- 是啊 - 尴尬了
- Yeah. - Awkward.
那个 你们两之前也见过了 这是杰姬
Well, you two already sorta met, but this is Jackie,
我的 呃...我不知道怎么叫你
my, uh... I don't know what to call you.
呃 女朋友?
Um, girlfriend?
- 女朋友? - 女朋友?
- Girlfriend? - Girlfriend?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
纯备胎 她根本算不了什么的
Total rebound. She means nothing to him.
简 别再试着圆场了 好吗?
Jane, stop trying to fix everything, okay?
我跟戴夫已经玩完了
Dave and I are through.
呃 加冰伏特加装在水杯里
Um, I'm gonna need vodka in a water glass with ice,
我基本今晚都会要"水"的
and I'm gonna be ordering "water" from you all night long,
所以 给我一杯"水" 谢谢
so one water please.
立即生效还是你现在真的想要水?
Did we start already or do you really want water?
- 伏特加 - 好的
Just bring me vodka.  Okay.
杰姬 我喜欢你的帽子
So, Jackie, love your hat.
谢谢 《明星伙伴》里的特特尔亲笔签名的哦
Thanks. It's signed by Turtle from "Entourage."
你有那么棒的帽子么你?啊?
What are you wearing that's so great, huh?
嘿!大家好啊!
Hey, everybody!  Hi!
喂 你们两 看在彭妮的面上表现好点
Hey, you two, at least keep it together for Penny's sake.
- 生日快乐! - 嘿 天啊!
- Happy Birthday!  - Hey! Oh, my God!
嘿 大家 这是托德
Hey, guys.  So, um, this is Todd.
这是阿历克斯 简 马克斯和...
And this is Alex, Jane, Max, Dave, and...
嘿
Hey.
杰姬  戴夫女朋友
Jackie, Dave's girlfriend.
很高兴再次见面啊
Great to see you again.
彭妮跟我说了很多关于你们的事
Penny has told me so much about you guys.
很多哈
So much.
你们能这么亲密真好 很难得
It's awesome how close you all are. Really special.
我去洗下手 离开一下 好吗 宝贝?
I'm just gonna run and wash my hands, okay, babe?
嗯 去吧
Mm. Go.
去吧
Mm. Get outta here.
怎么样...他是不是非常"迷银"啊?
So... isn't he ah-mah-zing?
人看起来很好啊 而且超级性感的说
- He seems really great and superhot.
噢 那家伙是弯的
Aw. That dude is gay.
- 啥? - 他一进门就开始电我
- Sorry?  - He gave me gay eyes, like, right away.
我是说 他比戴夫的外套都钙
I mean, that dude is gayer than Dave's jacket.
好吧 他如果是钙男我肯定会知道
Okay, I think I would know if he was gay.
彭妮得了吧 你之前不也不知道我是么
Penny, come on, you had no idea that I was gay.
这感觉太正点了
This just feels so right.
完全同意
Totally.
彭妮我只是替你着想 好吗?
Penny, I'm just looking out for you, okay?
直男干嘛进门没事洗手啊?
And what straight guy washes his hands?
抱歉这么久 煤灰洗也洗不干净
Sorry. It's just so hard to get the soot off.
我是个消防志愿者
I'm a volunteer fireman.
对 对 很好的理由
Yep, yep. There it is.
生日快乐 派对妞们!
Happy Birthday, party people!
如狼似虎的30岁了哈!
Dirty 30!
我还以为你只有26岁啊
I thought you were turning 26.
我是还只有26岁
I am turning 26.
开玩笑呢?
What?
哦 当真的
Oh, you're serious.
我也好想一下子26岁哦
I can't wait to be 26.
我觉得都没有人把你当真的
I feel like nobody really takes you seriously
如果还是高中生的话
when you're still in high school.
服务员 这儿来一杯水
Waitress, another water when you get a chance.
原来还只有26这么年轻啊
That bitch young.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
嗯
你怎么看托德啊?
What do you think about Todd?
他不是弯男 对吧?
He's not gay, right?
杰姬 你长大后想干嘛?
So, Jackie, what do you want to be when you grow up?
我想当个兽医
I either want to be a veterinarian
也想主持个真人秀
or have a reality show.
哇! 真了不起
Wow! Those are things.
快说点什么 那么..你们俩是在哪认识的?
Say something.  So...Where'd you two lovebirds meet?
世纪佳缘~ 我们立刻就来电了
jDate. We instantly connected.
我勒个去 我还以为只犹太人才上那个网站捏
Oh, I thought you had to be Jewish to be on that thing.
我就是个犹太人
I am Jewish.
不 我刚刚在跟彭妮讲话
-No, I I was talking about Penny.
嘿 哦也! 原来彭妮也是犹太人啊
Hey.  Yeah! Penny's also Jewish.
呀! 也! 猜对啦! 二十六岁的犹太妞
Yay! Yeah! All right! 26-year-old Jew.
还有什么是我不知道的 嗯 彭妮彭 彭?
Anything else I need to know, uh, Penny Pen Pen?
还有怎么看电子邮件的标签...
Just how to read e-mails labeled...
"紧急 宴会 闭嘴"
"urgent party deets."
犹太老兄是我菜 你懂的
You know, Jewish dudes are my jam.
就像穆斯林什叶派的拉比夫
Like that Shia LaBeef.
人家喜欢跟他联系 嗯哼?
I'd love to connect with him, huh?
托德 对不对? 我觉得我说对了
Am I right, Todd? I think I'm right.
-老兄 我才不是 -是吗 你真的不是么?
- I'm more of a Megan Fox guy, bro.  - Oh, are you really?
好啦
Okay.
我们今天是来联谊的 对吗 托德?
It really is all about connecting, isn't it, Todd?
终于能见到你 真是太高兴了
I mean, we are so glad to finally meet you.
彭妮生日快乐
And, Penny, Happy Birthday.
知道吗 托德 我也想试一次
You know what? I would throw in one caveat, Todd.
你永远也不知道谁会闯进来 然后两人对上眼
You never know when someone else is gonna come in and connect
还是和已经跟你对上眼的那个
with the someone that you already connected with,
然后在不知情的情况下 视频网上面的昵称
and before you know it, your nickname on YouTube is
就变成了"婚礼蠢蛋"
"The Wedding Douche,"
然后你不得不背着包在外面逃难
and you're living out of a gym bag.
谢谢各位光临 仿佛就在昨天
Thanks for coming, everybody. It feels like only yesterday
1984年奥运会期间 我来到了人世
that I was born during the 1984 Olympics,
一个年轻的犹太生命
a young Jewess,
26年弹指一挥间呐
26 years ago.
知道吗 托德? 戴夫说的没错 世道变了
You know what, Todd? Dave is right. Things change.
因为工作的关系你不得不忍受他
You have to work at the relationship.
一个星期别洗两次澡
Don't shower twice a week and only focus
-专注你床上功夫就行了 -好
- on your stuff in bed. - Okay.
我真是个体贴的做爱对象
I am a very caring lovemaker.
-同意  -好戏开场!
-He is.  -Here we go!
我做的一切都是为了维持我们之间的关系
You know, all I did was work on our relationship.
你真是太难搞了
You're super high-maintenance.
等等 这么说阿历克斯就是落跑新娘咯?
Wait. So Alex is the runaway bride?
没错 美女 我就是那个落跑新娘
Yes, jailbait, I am the runaway bride,
我毁了一切 我也不知道
and I ruined everything for everybody. And I don't know
告诉你们什么好了 只是两分钟前
what to tell you except that two minutes before
我本来准备离开这儿的 简跟我讲
I'm supposed to walk out there, Jane's talking to me
她准备怀孕 准备搬到郊区去住的
about prepregnancy cleanses and moving to the suburbs.
我没有...我的确没有道歉 因为事实上
I don't... I don't have an excuse except for the fact that...
我也吓坏了 好吗?
I freaked out, okay?
伴娘做的很到位 简
Really great bridesmaid work, Jane.
戴夫 知道吗 如果仅仅几句话
You know, Dave, if a few sentences
就让一个新娘从你们的婚礼跑掉
can make a girl run out of your wedding,
只能怪你们的关系一开始就不牢固
you weren't really on solid ground in the first place.
你们的关系不牢固!
You're not on solid ground!
老兄 你还没走出来啊 大伙 来嘛 高兴点
Not your best comeback, bro. Come on, everybody. Chill, all right?
托德肯定觉得我们疯了(犹太语)
Todd must think we're meshugenah.
我刚那样说对吗 合不合时宜 彭?
Did I say that right, Pen? Right context?
是啊 嗯哼 -因为你是犹太人 -是啊
Yep. Uh-huh.-Because you're Jewish.  - Yes.
听着 阿历克斯宝贝 淡定
Look, Alex, honey, just calm down.  Okay.
-来喝点水 -嗯嗯...
-Have some water.  -Uh, mm...
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么搞的? 这杯是伏特加!
What the hell? This is all vodka!
什么? 服务员
What? Waiter.
-简 你喝酒了? -没啊 是你在喝酒
-Jane, you're drinking? -No, you're drinking.
每天晚上的禁欲
Night of a thousand comebacks.
你有没有想过我们的怀孕计划?
What about our cleanse?
我排除了一切身体和心理的杂念
I've had pure evil coming out of both ends of my body
整整三个星期了啊 你居然喝伏特加?
for three weeks, and you're drinking vodka?
我很抱歉 我只是..我..我不知道..我
I'm sorry. I just... I... I don't know. I...
我现在根本都不想怀孩子好吧?
I don't want to have a baby right now, okay?
我看到阿历克斯和戴夫准备要个孩子的时候
I did when I thought
也想要的
Alex and Dave were gonna have one
大家住隔壁 幸福的生活在一起
and live next door, and we were all gonna be happy together,
但是现在就只剩我们搬去乡下住
but now it's just gonna be us out there in the suburbs,
孤孤单单的 慢慢就放弃要孩子了
all alone, slowly giving up.
五年之后 我会梳着婆婆头
Five years later, I'm rocking butchy mom hair
开着我的紫色的福特风中之星
and dreaming about driving my burgundy windstar
穿过乡间作坊 马克斯住在圣菲达
through a farmer's market. And Max is living in Santa Fe
和 一个叫罗宾的家具商住在一起
with a furniture dealer named Robin.
这是个女孩的名字吗?
Is it a girl?
还是个小伙子? 我不知道 真的不知道
Is it a guy? I don't know. I don't know,
因为我们五年都没有说过话了!
'cause we haven't spoken in five years!
然后我碰到了彭妮在...
And then I run into Penny at...
在...在托德的追悼会上
at... at Todd's memorial.
哦 是的 他死了 但是不是救火死的...
Oh, yeah, he died, but not in a fire...
在一个殉公消防员家属的慈善晚宴上
In a charity bike-a-thon for families of dead firemen.
抱歉了 各位 太戏剧了 彭妮和我
Sorry, dude, rough twist.  And Penny and I
甚至都没有认出对方
don't even recognize each other
因为我很长时间没有见过她了
because I haven't seen her
-自从她三十岁生日宴会之后 -是二十六岁
- since her 30th birthday party.  - 26th.
这都是你的错 阿历克斯!
And it's all your fault, Alex!
好吧 这就是你喝伏特加时发生的一切
Well, that's what happens when you drink vodka
我现在满肚子的蔬菜汁
on a stomach full of cabbage juice.
把这个给我
Give me that.
嘿 牛肉兄
Hey, meat.  Mmm.
棒极了 阿力
Nice work, Al.
你真是破坏友谊界的迈克尔 乔丹
You're the Michael Jordan of destroying friendships.
是啊 那你就是跟未成年贱货鬼混的
Well, you're the Michael Jordan of
无耻淫徒中的迈克尔 乔丹
banging underage sluts.
我十八岁了 老女人
I'm 18, slut.
谁是迈克尔 乔丹?
And who's Michael Jordan?
天哪 你的朋友们真是帮傻帽
God, your friends are all so immature.
#祝你生日快乐 祝你生日快乐 生日快乐#
#Happy Birthday to you Happy Birthday to you Happy Birthday,
#亲爱的彭妮二十六岁生日快乐#
dear Penny Happy 26th birthday, Penny
我三十了 我是个天主教堂
I'm 30 and I'm Catholic
我会自己孤单的穿着一件闪亮的圣诞毛衣死去
and I'm gonna die alone in a light-up Christmas sweater,
跟动物园的鹦鹉去谈去吧
talking to a menagerie of parrots.
哦!
Oh!
Ooh!
-我现在完全摸不清头脑了 -我知道 淡定
-I'm so confused right now. -I know you are. Been there.
你会意识到...
And you will realize...
可能不是今天 也许也不是明天
may not be today, may not be tomorrow,
或者不是从现在开始的一个月 一年...
may not be a month from now or a year from now...
但是终有一天 你会意识到
But you will wake up one day and say,
"哇 哥喜欢男淫"
"Whoa. I like dudes."
如果真的那样的话 我很乐意你打电话给我
And when that happens, I would love it if you gave me a call.
我们可以一起去喝杯 然后看场电影神马的
We'll go get a beer. We'll rent a movie...
可能看"凯特和利奥波德"神马的
Maybe "Kate & Leopold."
老兄 我是直的 好吧?
Dude, I'm not gay, okay?
哇 真是个十足的恐同深柜
Whoa. What a homophobe.
一个有我号码的恐同深柜 谢谢~
A homophobe who now has my number, thank you.
你俩这是天合之作
Really excellent work, you two.
这真是我过得最糟糕的生日了
That was my worst birthday
自从我妈跟我前男友在假日乐园舌吻那次之后
since my mom frenched my boyfriend at Epcot.
那么 你百分之百确定托德是个同性恋?
So are you 100% sure Todd is gay?
百分之一百五
-150%.
我们昨天晚上告别的时候有点诡异
Our good-bye last night was a little weird.
哦 拜
Oh. Okay.
拜
Yeah.
有人跟戴夫和阿历克斯谈过吗
Has anyone talked to Dave or Alex?
嗯 戴夫就来了
Yeah, Dave's coming.
那么我们就不能叫阿历克斯了
-So that means we can't invite Alex?
哇 真是糟透了
Wow. This sucks.
-嘿 大伙 看呐 嗯哼? -嗨 各位
-Hey, guys. Check it out.  Huh? -Hi, guys.
是个好消息吧?
Right? Great news.
我们破镜重圆了 开玩笑的
We are back together. Just kidding.
我还是很讨厌她
I still hate her,
不过看在她昨晚花四个小时跟哥道歉的份上
but she did spend four hours apologizing last night,
-这真是个好的开始 -戴夫承认
-which was a pretty good start.  -And Dave did admit
他把我的存在当做理所当然的事了
that he's been taking me for granted for a while.
好吧 我承认
- I did,
但是我说过那是你应该在婚礼前谈的事
but I said that's the kind of stuff you talk about
是在婚礼前 不是在婚礼中哦
before the wedding, not at the wedding. And I pointed out
还有戴夫撒双人字拖
that Dave wore flip-flops
就去赴我父母结婚三十五周年的纪念宴会
to my parents' 35th anniversary.
嗯 那是跟黑领带一起的混搭
Mm. It was black-tie optional.
-又来了 -另一场血雨腥风啊
-Here we go again.  -Another double bloody.
童鞋们 这... 这都是我的错
Guys, this is... This is all my fault.
我对戴夫做的一切 真是 真是太过分了
And what I did to Dave was... was horrible,
你们懂的 但是我和戴夫说好了 我俩
you know, but... but Dave and I agree that that's between us,
如果这样还不如让我去死...
you know, and it would kill me if...
如果我成为大家以后不能一起混的罪魁祸首
If I'm the reason that we all can't hang out anymore.
是啊 我是说 我们大家都没有交新朋友
Yeah, I mean, none of us has made a new friend
在过去的十一年当中
in, like, 11 years.
我甚至都不知道怎么去交朋友了
- I wouldn't even know how to do that.
怎么做 就像在大街上随便找个人 开始聊天
What do you do, just, like, walk up to random people and go,
"嘿 废话一堆 喜欢体育吗?"
"Hey, blah, blah, blah. Sports"?
我想认识的唯一人选就是我老公
The only new person I wanna meet is my husband.
我有一次在这里 碰到一个老女人
I was once on this plane with this old lady,
她想跟我搭讪
and she tried talking to me.
-我就假装我残废了 -伙计
-I just pretended I had some kind of disability. -Buddy.
嘿 彭妮搞砸了你的生日我很抱歉
Hey, Penny, I'm sorry your birthday got ruined...
但是人家给你准备了个惊喜
But I got you something.
-嘿 是什么 溜冰鞋? -呕!
-Hey, what is it, rollerblades?  -Ugh!
好吧 我道歉
Okay, I apologize.  Ah, don't.
-好吧 -哦哦!
- Okay.  - Oh!
生日快乐哟!
Happy Birthday!  Hello!
哇 自从犹太教成年礼以来
Aw! I haven't been this happy
人家就没这么开心过
since my bar mitzvah.
你能坐着说话吗?
Can you sit down?
嗯 如果大家不介意的要话 我开动了
Mmm. Don't mind if I do-skis.
唔 不会吧
Uh, maybe you don't-skis.
老兄 你就不能歇一会儿不吃蛋糕啊
You might want to take a little vacation from the cake, bro.
我显胖吗?
Is this the chubby thing?
如果是这样的话 请当面告诉我
'Cause if it is, just say it to my face.
大伙觉得我胖吗?
Do you guys think I look fat?
好吧 说实话 有一点
Well, you got a couple extra pounds.
我觉得你挺健康的 我只在乎你的身体
-I think about your health. -I just worry about your health.
说真的 你像年轻时候的
To be perfectly honest, you look like
凯西 贝茨 (好莱坞女演员 非常丰满)
a young Kathy Bates.
哦 不 不 就像自暴自弃后暴饮暴食的Paul Rudd
Ooh. No, no, no. It's like if Paul Rudd gave up.
我就接手 人家不介意的
I'll take her. I do not mind.
-哦 你应该... -好吧
-Oh, you're supposed to...  -Okay.
哦噢!~
Whoo!
#哦 哦 哦 我喜欢她因为她独特的魅力#
#Oh, oh, oh I love her because she moves in her own way #
#哦 哦 哦 她来看我的演出#
#oh, oh, oh, she came to my show #
#倾听我的一切...#
#just to hear about my day Corrected by #